japantimes.co.jp 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy | The Japan Times

The Japan Times fully understands the importance of protecting personal information, and observes all applicable laws and regulations relating to privacy protection. We have designed this Privacy Policy to explain how we safeguard the privacy of our users.

## Principles

This Privacy Policy applies to all matters relating to the handling of personal information on the “The Japan Times Online” website (the “Website”), located at http://www.japantimes.co.jp/, which is operated by The Japan Times Ltd.

  * We will comply with all applicable laws and regulations concerning privacy protection in handling your personal information.
  * We will only collect your personal information by appropriate and fair means.
  * We will not use your personal information beyond the scope of the purpose of use that we have previously specified, unless you give your prior consent.
  * We will not provide third parties with your personal information unless you give your prior consent, other than as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy.
  * We will at all times assign responsibility for protection of personal information and development of our internal systems to a designated officer in order to help ensure appropriate management of personal information.
  * We will maintain appropriate safeguards to protect your personal information from improper disclosure or modification and from unauthorized access.
  * We will regularly review this Privacy Policy to help ensure that appropriate safeguards are maintained.
  * We will respond appropriately to requests from our users to disclose the personal information that we maintain concerning them, to correct any inaccuracies in such information and to cease use of their personal information.
  * This Privacy Policy does not apply to personal information that we may obtain in the course of news collection and reporting. However, with reference to the principles of the Personal Information Protection Law of Japan, we will handle any such personal information in a manner that we believe is appropriate.

## Handling of personal data

**Appropriate Collection**  
We will only collect your personal information by appropriate and fair methods.  
**Type of Information We Collect**  
The personal information we collect may include your full name, e-mail address, gender, year of birth, nationality, occupation, interests and purpose of use of the Website.  
**Purpose of Use**  
Personal information we collect may be used for the following purposes:  
Providing services on the Website (hereinafter called the “Online Services”) to customers and conducting related operations;  
Processing of customer applications for the Online Services for members;  
Responses to customer inquiries and complaints;  
Efforts to design and improve the Service customized to interests of consumers, including through sending questionnaires to customers (no personal information collected thereby will be disclosed to any third parties);  
Efforts to customize the Service to the interests of our users, including through sending questionnaires to customers (no personal information collected thereby will be disclosed to any third parties); and  
Notifications to contest winners.  
Before using personal information for any purpose other than those listed above, we will notify you to request your consent, and will not use your personal information for such other purpose unless you give your consent.  
If you do not wish for us to use your personal information for the purposes described in (4), (5) and (6) above, you may opt out of such uses.  
**Providing Information to Third Parties**  
We will not provide your personal information to any third party without your advance consent, except where such disclosure:  
Is in accordance with or required by applicable law;  
Is necessary for the protection of the safety or property of our users or the public, and it is difficult or impractical to obtain the consent of the individual;  
Is necessary for public health or education and it is difficult or impractical to obtain the consent of the individual;  
Is made in cooperation with national or local authorities, or an individual or entity appointed by such authorities to enforce the law or carry out legal process, and in which seeking the consent of the individual could affect such enforcement or legal process; or  
Is made pursuant to a merger, acquisition or other business combination.  
We may disclose aggregate information regarding users (not including personally identifiable information) to third parties that we believe to be reputable. Please also see “About Cookies” below.  
If we entrust an individual or entity with the handling of any personal information, we will exercise necessary and appropriate supervision over such individual or entity to ensure the security of such personal information.  
**Children**  
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian may e-mail us, and we will remove such information from our database and cease promotional contacts with the child.  
Please see “Contact for Inquiries and Complaints about the Handling of Personal Information” below for information on how to contact us.  
**About “Cookies”  
**The Japan Times uses “cookies”— small files that the web browsers store on your computer — to manage access to and use of our site, recognize your preferences and to facilitate effective site administration.  
Some of the services and advertisements included in our site are delivered or served by third-party companies. These companies may place or recognize cookies, Web beacons or other technology to track certain non-personal information about our website users. You may opt out of their use by modifying the configuration of your web browser.  
We use Google Adsense to serve some advertisements on our site. Google uses cookies to display ads based on your visit to The Japan Times website and other sites. You may opt out of the use of this cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences "Google ad and content network privacy policy").  
We use Teads to deliver some of the advertisements displayed on our website. This ad-serving system may note some of the pages you visit through the use of pixel tags (also called “clear gifs”). In the course of serving advertisements to this site, Teads may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer in order to bring to you more relevant information and to make sure that you do not receive the same ad many times in the same session. To find out more about this sensing method and to know your choices about not having this information used by Teads, please visit [http://teads.tv/#/ja/privacy_policy](http://teads.tv/#/ja/privacy_policy)[  
](http://teads.tv/#/privacy_policy)**Analytics**  
We use Google Analytics to help analyze how users use our site. The tool uses cookies to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the site (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the site and to compile statistical reports on website activity for us. Google may also use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.  
**Security  
**To protect the personal information we collect from threats of improper disclosure or modification and from unauthorized access, and to maintain data accuracy, we have established appropriate physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy and our security standards and procedures on a regular basis in order to maintain appropriate safeguards. We will post any such changes on the Website, so please be sure to check back periodically.  
**Accountability  
**We have appointed a Privacy Officer, and endeavor to safeguard the privacy of our users and ensure compliance with the requirements of applicable laws relating to privacy protection.  
We instruct our management and employees concerning legal requirements and company regulations related to privacy protection as part of our continuing efforts to manage personal information appropriately.  
**Disclosure, Addition, Correction, Deletion  
**When we are requested by a user in accordance with procedures we have specified:  
to disclose his/her personal information, we will disclose such information as soon as practicable, unless such disclosure would be in violation of law.  
to correct, add to, or delete his/her personal information on the basis that such information is inaccurate, we will review the facts relating to such request without delay and will correct, add to, or delete the information on the basis of such review.  
Please see “How to Obtain Disclosure, Add to, Delete or Opt Out of Use of Your Personal Information” below for the procedures to make such a request.  
**Suspension of Use  
**When we are requested by a user to stop using his/her personal information on the basis that such information was collected improperly or is being used for purposes other than those specified without his/her consent, we will review the facts relating to such request without delay. If we find a valid reason for such request, we will cease use of such personal information.  
Please see “How to Obtain Disclosure, Add to, Delete or Opt Out of Use of Your Personal Information” below for the procedures to make such a request.  
**Inquiries and Complaints  
**We have established an office in order to receive and respond to any inquiries and complaints concerning our handling of personal information efficiently and appropriately. Please note that any such communications must be in writing (which may include e-mail).  
Please see “Contact for Inquiries and Complaints about the Handling of Personal Information” below for information on how to contact us.

**How to Obtain Disclosure, Add to, Delete or Opt Out of Use of Your Personal Information**

  1. Obtain an Application Form for Disclosure
  2. Complete and Send the Application Form  
Fill in the information requested and send the Application Form to our Information Desk with: 
    1. A deposit of five hundred yen (500 yen) by postal money order;
    2. A return envelope with your name and address; and
    3. Copies of two of the following documents to verify the identity of the person making the request: driver’s license, passport, foreign resident registration card, basic resident registration card with photo, pension insurance booklet or certificate of seal registration.

* In the event that the request is made by an agent, a document certifying the authority of the agent and copies of two of the documents above verifying the identity of the agent are required.

**Address**  
Information Desk for Disclosure and Opt Out  
The Japan Times Co., Ltd.  
5-4, Shibaura 4-chome Minato-ku, Tokyo, 108-8071

  3. We will send you a reply by registered mail.

## Contact for Inquiries and Complaints about the Handling of Personal Information

Contact us at The Japan Times Co., Ltd.  
5-4, Shibaura 4-chome Minato-ku, Tokyo, 108-8071

or [via this online form. ](http://awsadmin.japantimes.co.jp/contact-us/)
